sogoodblog.com 2016-12-25

# Privacy Policy - So Good Blog

So Good Blog is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the So Good Blog Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the So Good Blog website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information

So Good Blog collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. So Good Blog also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your postal address, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by So Good Blog. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by So Good Blog for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the So Good Blog Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through So Good Blog public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: So Good Blog does not read any of your private online communications.

So Good Blog encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from So Good Blog so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. So Good Blog is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the So Good Blog and So Good Blog family of Web sites.

Use of your Personal Information

So Good Blog collects and uses your personal information to operate the So Good Blog Web site and deliver the services you have requested. So Good Blog also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from So Good Blog and its affiliates. So Good Blog may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

So Good Blog does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. So Good Blog may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, So Good Blog may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to So Good Blog, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

So Good Blog keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within So Good Blog, in order to determine what So Good Blog services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within So Good Blog to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

So Good Blog Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on So Good Blog or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of So Good Blog; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of So Good Blog, or the public.

Withdrawing Your Consent

You may notify us at any time that you wish to withdraw or change your consent to our use and disclosure or your information. We will accommodate your request subject to legal and contractual restrictions related to your transactions. If you have “opted in” or subscribed to one of our newsletters or mailing lists, we will always provide you the opportunity to “opt out” or unsubscribe. For example, each e-newsletter we send to you will include a link or other method to unsubscribe or decline further e-newsletters.

Use of Cookies

The So Good Blog Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize So Good Blog pages, or register with So Good Blog site or services, a cookie helps So Good Blog to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same So Good Blog Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the So Good Blog features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the So Good Blog services or Web sites you visit.

Security of your Personal Information

So Good Blog secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. So Good Blog secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Changes to this Statement

So Good Blog will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. So Good Blog encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how So Good Blog is protecting your information.
